A Guide to the Papers of The Colson-Hill Family
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Edna Colson(Personal, Colson/Meredith, Education, Employment) 1905-1984
  - Correspondence Education
    - Colson- Dissertation Research Jan-Mar 1936 (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Colson- Dissertation Draft 1 (Box-folder 34:4)
    - Colson- Dissertation Draft 2 (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Colson- Dissertation Draft 3 (Box-folder 34:6)
    - Colson- Dissertation Draft (Box-folder 34:7)
    - Colson- Dissertation Digest 1939 (Box-folder 34:8)
    - Colson Non Official Publication at Columbia (Box-folder 34:9)
      - a. The Education Vanguard 1936
      - b. Red Research 1934
      - Columbia Alumni news
    - Colson-Official Publication Columbia: The Weekly Bulletin (Box-folder 34:10)
  - Correspondence Employment(VSU)
    - Colson/Gandy 1917-1973 (Box-folder 35:1)
    - Colson/Gandy 1924-1925 (Box-folder 35:2)
    - Colson/Gandy 1926-1927 (Box-folder 35:3)
    - Colson/Gandy 1928-1929 (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Colson/Gandy 1930-1931 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Colson/Gandy 1932 (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Colson/Gandy 1933-1934 (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Colson/Gandy 1935-1936 (Box-folder 35:8)
    - Colson/Gandy 1937 (Box-folder 35:9)
    - Colson/Gandy 1938 (Box-folder 35:10)
    - Colson/Gandy 1939-1942 (Box-folder 35:11)
    - Colson/Foster 1944-1949 (Box-folder 35:12)
    - Colson/David 1950-1956 (Box-folder 35:13)
    - Colson/VSU Foundation 1976-1981 (Box-folder 35:14)
    - VSU Declaration of Areas 1975-1976 (Box-folder 35:15)
    - Colson/Law 1979-1981 (Box-folder 35:16)
    - A.A.U.W 1953-1956 (Box-folder 36:1)
    - Administrative Policies 1943 (Box-folder 36:2)
    - Alumna "Mildred Brown Williams" 1963 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - Annual Reports, Minutes (D.A. Wilkerson) 1930 (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Annual Reports,Minutes (D.A. Wilkerson) 1934-1935 (Box-folder 36:5)
    - Annual Reports,Minutes (D.A. Wilkerson) 1935-1940 (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Aims of the Virginia State Faculty Study (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Budgets (Art) 1932-1936 (Box-folder 36:8)
    - Budgets (David) 1950-1953 (Box-folder 36:9)
    - Budgets (Division of Education) 1936-1937 (Box-folder 36:10)
    - Budgets (Miscellaneous) 1933-1936 (Box-folder 36:11)
    - Budget (P.E. Sports) (Box-folder 36:12)
    - Budget Proposal 1933-1936 (Box-folder 36:13)
    - Budget (Statement Loan Fund) (Box-folder 36:14)
    - Budgets Student Activity Fund 1930-1932 (Box-folder 36:15)
    - Budgets Student Activity Fund 1933-1936 (Box-folder 36:16)
    - Budget for student groups (Box-folder 36:17)
    - Cannon, David (Box-folder 36:18)
    - Committee on Commission (Box-folder 36:19)
    - VSU- Cannon, David 1936-1938 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - VSU- Campus Womens Organizations Annual Report 1954-1958 (Box-folder 37:2)
    - VSU- Characteristics of a good Elementary School (Box-folder 37:3)
    - Cheyney AACTE 1953-1954 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Chesterfield County (Box-folder 37:5)
    - Congress Hotel AACTE (Box-folder 37:6)
    - Congress Hotel AACTE 1947-1955 (Box-folder 37:7)
    - Collegiate Education (Negro Education) 1924 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - American Education Week 1959 (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Community Study (Petersburg) (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Community Study (Petersburg) (Box-folder 37:11)
    - Founders Day 1943 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Founders Day Notes 1943 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Founders Day Notes 1943 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - VSU- High School Principal Conference Feb-Mar 1940 (Box-folder 38:4)
    - VSU- Virginia Conference for Family References 1940-1941 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - VSU- Cadet Teaching Program 1952 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - VSU- County Training School Circular #2 1919 (Box-folder 38:7)
    - VSU- Correspondence 1954-1964 (Box-folder 38:8)
    - VSU- Correspondence- Elementary Eduaction 1950-1952 (Box-folder 38:9)
    - VSU- Correpondence- School 1942-1954 (Box-folder 38:10)
    - VSU- Curriculum Committee 1950 (Box-folder 38:11)
    - VSU- Curriculum Activities 1930 (Box-folder 38:12)
    - VSU-Curriculum Activities 1931-1933 (Box-folder 38:13)
    - VSU- Extension Correspondence 1924-1939 (Box-folder 38:14)
    - VSU-Faculty Conference 1941 (Box-folder 38:15)
    - VSU- Faculty Conference 1941 (Box-folder 38:16)
    - VSU- Fiftieth Anniversary Publication 1933 (Box-folder 38:17)
    - Johnston, James Hugo Jr. (Box-folder 39:1)
    - Johnston, James Hugo Jr. 1942 (Box-folder 39:2)
    - Dean Johnston Registration 1952 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Dept. of Elementary Education 1952 (Box-folder 39:4)
    - Dinning Room Committee 1933 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Elementary Education, Committee Reports and minutes 1936-1950 (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Education News 1950 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - Elementary Education 1932,1950 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Elementary Education (minute and correspondence) 1948-1952 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - Elementary Education Club 1941,1946 (Box-folder 39:10)
    - Elementary Education Department 1949-1950 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - Elementary Practice Teaching 1938-1945 (Box-folder 39:12)
    - VSu- Executive Council 1931 (Box-folder 39:13)
    - Extension Dept 1944 (Box-folder 39:14)
    - VSU- Graduate Committee 1936-1938 (Box-folder 40:1)
    - VSU- Graduate Committee Nov 1938-1940 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - VSU- Graduate Committee Minutes 1937-1938 (Box-folder 40:3)
    - VSU-Graduate Committee Minutes and Reports 1939 (Box-folder 40:4)
    - VSU- Graduates Committee Minutes (Box-folder 40:5)
    - VSU- Graduate Committee Minutes (Box-folder 40:6)
    - VSU- Guidance (Box-folder 40:7)
    - VSU- Guidance 1945 (Box-folder 40:8)
    - VSU- Hamlin, Wilhemina 1931-1971 (Box-folder 40:9)
    - VSU- Harris, Viola Belle 1932-1970 (Box-folder 40:10)
    - Colson- Hawkins, Helen 1935 (Box-folder 40:11)
    - Colson- Helen Baker 1968 (Box-folder 40:12)
    - Colson- Thompson, Journal of Negro Education 1932-1939 (Box-folder 40:13)
    - Colson- Henderson, Ruth 1934-1943 (Box-folder 40:14)
    - VSU- The High School Torch 1935 (Box-folder 40:15)
    - Colson- Howard, Roscoe 1934 (Box-folder 40:16)
    - Colson- Howeston, Ethel M. 1931-1935 (Box-folder 40:17)
    - Colson- Hunter, J.M. 1931-1932 (Box-folder 40:18)
    - Colson- Hunter, M.E.V. 1931-1935 (Box-folder 40:19)
    - Colson- Interracial 1954 (Box-folder 40:20)
    - Colson- Jackson, Marjory 1933 (Box-folder 40:21)
    - colson- Jackson, Wallace 1967 (Box-folder 40:22)
    - The Lagraac Lunch Club 1962-1963 (Box-folder 41:1)
    - Letters Feb. 1930-1935 (Box-folder 41:2)
    - Letters 1935-1943 (Box-folder 41:3)
    - Training School (Campus) 1925 (Box-folder 41:4)
    - Library Committe 1933,1942 (Box-folder 41:5)
    - Lockett, John L. 1933 (Box-folder 41:6)
    - Matoaca lab 1955 (Box-folder 41:7)
    - Methods in Public School Music Report (Box-folder 41:8)
    - Mifflin, Houghton 1929-1934 (Box-folder 41:9)
    - Miscellaneous 1947 (Box-folder 41:10)
    - Music Courses 1930-1940 (Box-folder 41:11)
    - Music Courses (High School) 1930-1940 (Box-folder 41:12)
    - Play- History of VSU (Box-folder 41:13)
    - Post War Planning (Founders Day) 1942-Jan 1943 (Box-folder 41:14)
    - Post War Planning (Founders Day) 1943 (Box-folder 41:15)
    - Prom-Senior Dance (Hardy) 1934,1937 (Box-folder 41:16)
    - Radio Program 1950 (Box-folder 41:17)
    - Recreation Department (Box-folder 41:18)
    - Reflections 1954 (Box-folder 41:19)
    - Report of Committee Southern Negro Youth 1933 (Box-folder 41:20)
    - Report, State Board of Education 1939 (Box-folder 41:21)
    - Report State Conference on Adult Education 1950 (Box-folder 42:1)
    - Report Sub- Committee in Academic Affairs (Box-folder 42:2)
    - Annual Report Supervisor of Negro Education 1941-1942 (Box-folder 42:3)
    - Research in Southern Education 1949 (Box-folder 42:4)
    - Resume of State Wide Conference 1947-1948 (Box-folder 42:5)
    - Training School Roster (Box-folder 42:6)
    - Secondary Education 1953 (Box-folder 42:7)
    - Senior Scope D. Webster Davis H.S. 1937 (Box-folder 42:8)
    - Social Economic Study of Negro 1939 (Box-folder 42:9)
    - The Story of Money 1952 (Box-folder 42:10)
    - Summer School (Courses, Schedules, Staff) 1932-1949 (Box-folder 42:11)
    - Summer School (Courses,Schedules,Staff) 1950 (Box-folder 42:12)
    - Sunday School 1918-1925 (Box-folder 42:13)
    - Teachers Schedule 1937-1953 (Box-folder 42:14)
    - Virginia Union University 1942,1962 (Box-folder 42:15)
    - Virgie Brown Sparks 1958 (Box-folder 42:16)
    - Wilkerson, Doseyw 1941 (Box-folder 42:17)
    - Miscellaneous 1926-1981 (Box-folder 42:18)
    - Newbold 1931-1934 (Box-folder 42:19)
    - Newsome 1932 (Box-folder 42:20)
    - Normal School Standards 1930 (Box-folder 42:21)
    - Principals Conference 1938 (Box-folder 42:22)
    - Va. Comm. On Interracial-Cooperation 1943 (Box-folder 42:23)
    - Work V.S.U Senior Song 1940 (Box-folder 42:24)
    - A-Adult Education 1924-1941 (Box-folder 43:1)
    - A- Adult Education (Box-folder 43:2)
    - B- 1920 (Box-folder 43:3)
    - C- Carney, M. 1920,1946 (Box-folder 43:4)
    - C- Committee (Logan) 1925 (Box-folder 43:5)
    - C- 1934-1937 (Box-folder 43:6)
    - C- Class Committee 1934 (Box-folder 43:7)
    - C- Committee on Dinning Hall (Box-folder 43:8)
    - C- (Extension Committee) (Box-folder 43:9)
    - C- (Committee-Guidance) 1935 (Box-folder 43:10)
    - C- (Committee on Student Conference) 1954 (Box-folder 43:11)
    - C-(Inter.Inst. Faculty Committee) 1953 (Box-folder 43:12)
    - C- (Music Committee) (Box-folder 43:13)
    - C- (Prudential Committee) 1925-1926 (Box-folder 43:14)
    - C- (Committee on Regulation) 1925 (Box-folder 43:15)
    - D- (Dillard) 1925-1955 (Box-folder 43:16)
    - D- (Jackson,Davis) 1936-1941 (Box-folder 43:17)
    - E- 1925-1932 (Box-folder 43:18)
    - E- 1933 (Box-folder 43:19)
    - E- 1934 (Box-folder 43:20)
    - E- (Earson) 1935 (Box-folder 44:1)
    - E- 1936 (Box-folder 44:2)
    - E- 1937 (Box-folder 44:3)
    - E- 1938 (Box-folder 44:4)
    - F- Luther H. 1928 (Box-folder 44:5)
    - F- Fisk University 1928-1937 (Box-folder 44:6)
    - F- Fisk University 1933 (Box-folder 44:7)
    - F- Fisk University 1936 (Box-folder 44:8)
    - F- (Box-folder 44:9)
    - F- (Pins and Rings) Correspondence 1930-1932 (Box-folder 44:10)
    - F- (Pins and Rings) Correspondence 1933 (Box-folder 44:11)
    - F- (Pins and Rings) Correspondence 1934 (Box-folder 44:12)
    - F- (Pins and Rings) Correspondence 1935-1936 (Box-folder 44:13)
    - F- (Pins and Rings) Receipts and Lists 1934-1936 (Box-folder 44:14)
    - F- Reports (Student Loan Fund) 1935 (Box-folder 44:15)
    - G- 1930-1934 (Box-folder 44:16)
    - G- 1933-1937 (Box-folder 44:17)
    - H- 1924-1934 (Box-folder 44:18)
    - H- 1935 (Box-folder 44:19)
    - J- Johnson, C.S. 1925-1931 (Box-folder 45:1)
    - J- Johnson, C.S. 1932 (Box-folder 45:2)
    - J- Johnson, C.S. 1933-1934 (Box-folder 45:3)
    - J- Johnson, C.S. 1935-1936 (Box-folder 45:4)
    - K- 1925 (Box-folder 45:5)
    - L- 1933-1937 (Box-folder 45:6)
    - M- 1925-1931 (Box-folder 45:7)
    - M- 1932 (Box-folder 45:8)
    - M- 1933 (Box-folder 45:9)
    - M- 1934 (Box-folder 45:10)
    - M- 1935 (Box-folder 45:11)
    - M- 1936 (Box-folder 45:12)
    - M- 1937 (Box-folder 45:13)
    - M- 1938 (Box-folder 45:14)
    - M- 1939 (Box-folder 45:15)
    - M- 1940 (Box-folder 45:16)
    - M- 1941,1943 (Box-folder 45:17)
    - N- 1925,1930 (Box-folder 45:18)
    - P- 1920-1931 (Box-folder 45:19)
    - P- 1932 (Box-folder 45:20)
    - P- Jun-Dec 1932 (Box-folder 45:21)
    - P- 1933 (Box-folder 45:22)
    - P-O 1927 (Box-folder 46:1)
    - P- Jan-July 1933 (Box-folder 46:2)
    - P- Aug- Dec 1933 (Box-folder 46:3)
    - P- 1934 (Box-folder 46:4)
    - P- 1935,1939 (Box-folder 46:5)
    - P- 1936-1953 (Box-folder 46:6)
    - P- (Course in School Hygiene) (Box-folder 46:7)
    - P- (Psyc. Program) (Box-folder 46:8)
    - P- (Correspondence) 1925 (Box-folder 46:9)
    - R- (Reynolds C.I.C.) 1925-1933 (Box-folder 46:10)
    - R- 1934 (Box-folder 46:11)
    - R- 1935-1941 (Box-folder 46:12)
    - R- Publications 1935 (Box-folder 46:13)
    - R- Report 1945 (Box-folder 46:14)
    - S- 1925 (Box-folder 46:15)
    - S- 1929-1932 (Box-folder 46:16)
    - S- 1933-1935 (Box-folder 46:17)
    - S- 1936-1939 (Box-folder 47:1)
    - S- Colson speaking at Sweet Briar 1940-1941 (Box-folder 47:2)
    - T- 1925-1931 (Box-folder 47:3)
    - V- 1923-1930 (Box-folder 47:4)
    - V- 1931-1932 (Box-folder 47:5)
    - V- 1933-1936 (Box-folder 47:6)
    - V- 1937-1938 (Box-folder 47:7)
    - V- (Box-folder 47:8)
    - W- 1922-1931 (Box-folder 47:9)
    - W- Feb-Sept 1932 (Box-folder 47:10)
    - W- Oct- Dec 1933 (Box-folder 47:11)
    - W- Jan-June 1933 (Box-folder 47:12)
    - W- 1934 (Box-folder 47:13)
    - W- 1935 (Box-folder 47:14)
    - W- 1936 (Box-folder 47:15)
    - W- 1937 (Box-folder 47:16)
    - W- 1938 (Box-folder 47:17)
    - W- 1939-1941 (Box-folder 47:18)
    - Y- 1931-1934 (Box-folder 47:19)
- Organizations and Affiliations of Edna MEade Colson Edna Meade Colson
  - The Virginia Federation of Colored Womens Clubs
    - Virginia Federation History Petersburg Chapter (Box-folder 48:1)
    - Virginia Federation Campus Club Ministers 1940-1946 (Box-folder 48:2)
    - Virginia Federation Ministers (VSFCW) Junior Dept. 1934 (Box-folder 48:3)
    - Virginia Federation Committee, Women in Industry (Box-folder 48:4)
    - Virginia Federation Hospitality Committee 1968 (Box-folder 48:5)
    - Virginia Federation Planning Committee 1975 (Box-folder 48:6)
    - Virginia Federation Paper (Speech) 1955 (Box-folder 48:7)
    - Virginia Federation Committee General (Box-folder 48:8)
    - Virginia Federation Financial Records 1964-1970 (Box-folder 48:9)
    - Virginia Federation Petersburg Programs (Printed) 1970-1971 (Box-folder 48:10)
    - Virginia Federation Reports 1956-1957,1958-1959 (Box-folder 48:11)
    - Virginia Federation Reports- Central State Hospital 1956-1970 (Box-folder 48:12)
    - Virginia State College Education Club 1932 (Box-folder 48:13)
    - Virginia Federation Programs- Petersburg Chapter Frontiers Club 1958 (Box-folder 48:14)
    - Virginia Federation Art Committee 1971 (Box-folder 48:15)
    - Virginia Federation Correspondence- United Charity Inc. (Box-folder 48:16)
    - Virginia Federation Meeting, Schedule and Agendas 1958 (Box-folder 48:17)
    - Virginia Federation United Citizens Council 1955-1956 (Box-folder 48:18)
    - Virginia Federation Women's Council Petersburg, VA 1958,1978 (Box-folder 48:19)
    - Virginia Federation Citizen Committee 1966,1971 (Box-folder 48:20)
    - Virginia Federation Report Women of the Year Committee 1957-1958 (Box-folder 48:21)
      - Virginia State College Education Club (Minutes) 1932
      - The Women Council of Petersburg Virginia State Federation of Colored Women Clubs (Minutes) Sept-Oct 1942
      - The Women Coucil of Petersburg 1956-1961
      - The Virginia Federation of Colored Women Clubs (Minutes) 1956-1961
      - The Junior Women Federation Club (Minutes) 1937-1938
    - Virginia Federation Constitution 1960 (Box-folder 49:1)
    - Virginia Federation Awards 1963 (Box-folder 49:2)
    - Virginia Federation, The College Girls Scout Code (Box-folder 49:3)
    - Virginia Federation Newsletters (PIA) 1962-1965 (Box-folder 49:4)
    - Virginia Federation Membership List 1957-1962 (Box-folder 49:5)
    - Virginia Federation Annual Report 1957,1962 (Box-folder 49:6)
    - Virginia Federation Bulletin 1949,1970 (Box-folder 49:7)
    - Virginia Federation, Annual Meetings 1962,1969 (Box-folder 49:8)
    - Virginia Federation, Annual Convention 1960,1975 (Box-folder 49:9)
    - Virginia Federation Annual Conference Reports and Minutes 1943,1947 (Box-folder 49:10)
    - Virginia State Federation of Colored Womens Club (History including Petersburg) (Box-folder 49:11)
    - Virginia Federation Programs 1956,1961 (Box-folder 49:12)
    - Virginia Federation State Wide Programs 1957,1960 (Box-folder 49:13)
    - Virginia Federation Song-Creed (Box-folder 49:14)
    - Virginia Federation- Printed Programs 1946 (Box-folder 49:15)
    - Virginia Federation- Printed Programs 1956,1958,1971 (Box-folder 49:16)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1933-1934 (Box-folder 49:17)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1936-1939 (Box-folder 49:18)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1940 (Box-folder 49:19)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 49:20)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 49:21)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1943-1945 (Box-folder 49:22)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1946,1950 (Box-folder 49:23)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1951 (Box-folder 49:24)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1952 (Box-folder 50:1)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1953 (Box-folder 50:2)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 50:3)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 50:4)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder 50:5)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 50:6)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder 50:7)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1959 (Box-folder 50:8)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder 50:9)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder 50:10)
    - Virginia Federation-Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 50:11)
    - Correspondence-Virginia Federation 1963 (Box-folder 50:12)
    - Correspondence 1963 (Box-folder 51:1)
    - Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box-folder 51:2)
    - Correspondence 1967 (Box-folder 51:3)
    - Correspondence 1970 (Box-folder 51:4)
    - Correspondence 1971-1977 (Box-folder 51:5)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 51:6)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club 1939-1946 (Box-folder 51:7)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club Nov 1951 (Box-folder 51:8)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club (Minutes) 1940,1945 (Box-folder 51:9)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club (Miscellaneous) 1933-1945 (Box-folder 51:10)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club (Miscellaneous) 1946-1947 (Box-folder 51:11)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club Reports 1920,1946-1947 (Box-folder 51:12)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club (News Clippings) (Box-folder 51:13)
    - Correspondence-Campus Club (News clippings) (Box-folder 51:14)
    - Campus Club Programs 1936,1946 (Box-folder 51:15)
    - Campus Club Speech (Box-folder 51:16)
    - Campus History 1937 (Box-folder 51:17)
    - Virginia Federation - PTSVSC 1958-1971 (Box-folder 52:1)
    - Virginia Federation - PTSVSC-TB 1962-1963 (Box-folder 52:2)
    - Virginia Federation - PTSVSC Minutes 1962-1973 (Box-folder 52:3)
    - Virginia Federation - PTSVSC 1964 (Box-folder 52:4)
    - Virginia Federation - PTSVSC 1966 (Box-folder 52:5)
    - Virginia Federation (Printed) 1972 (Box-folder 52:6)
    - Training School (newsletters) 1961 (Box-folder 52:7)
    - Training School (newsletters) 1962 (Box-folder 52:8)
    - Training School (newsletters) 1963-1964 (Box-folder 52:9)
    - Training School (newsletters) 1966-1967 (Box-folder 52:10)
    - Training School (newsletters) 1967-1969 (Box-folder 52:11)
    - May Day Program 1957 (Box-folder 52:12)
    - The Virginia Federation of Colored Women's Club Anuual Meetings, Programs,and Minutes (Othertype 53)
    - Newport News,VA 1942 (Othertype 53)
    - Salem, VA 1955 (Othertype 53)
    - Charlottesville,VA 1959 (Othertype 53)
    - Portsmouth,VA 1960 (Othertype 53)
    - Petersburg,VA 1962 (Othertype 53)
  - The National Association of College Women 1925-1977
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1925-1929 (Box-folder 54:1)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1930 (Box-folder 54:2)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1931-1932 (Box-folder 54:3)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1933-1934 (Box-folder 54:4)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1935,1946 (Box-folder 54:5)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1947-1948 (Box-folder 54:6)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1947-1948 (Box-folder 54:6)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1950-1951 (Box-folder 54:7)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1952-1953 (Box-folder 54:8)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1954-1955 (Box-folder 54:9)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder 54:10)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1957-1959 (Box-folder 54:11)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1960-1961 (Box-folder 54:12)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1964-1967 (Box-folder 54:13)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1968 (Box-folder 54:14)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1969 (Box-folder 54:15)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1970-1972 (Box-folder 54:16)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box-folder 54:17)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence 1975-1977 (Box-folder 54:18)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence (Box-folder 54:19)
    - N.A.C.W-Correspondence-Photographs (Box-folder 54:20)
    - Chapter Records (Constitution) 1947 (Box-folder 55:1)
    - Chapter Records (Constitution) (Box-folder 55:2)
    - Chapter Records Minutes 1931 (Box-folder 55:3)
    - Chapter Records Minutes 1946,1947 (Box-folder 55:4)
    - Chapter Records Reports 1946,1962 (Box-folder 55:5)
    - Chapter Records Financial Reports (Box-folder 55:6)
    - Chapter Records Annual Convention 1932-1933 (Box-folder 55:7)
    - Chapter Records Convention Funding 1933 (Box-folder 55:8)
    - Chapter Records Committee Standards 1942 (Box-folder 55:9)
    - Chapter Records Annual Convention 1947 (Box-folder 55:10)
    - Chapter Records Sentenced Conference 1941 (Box-folder 55:11)
    - Chapter Records Printed 1946,1969 (Box-folder 55:12)
    - Chapter Records Roosters 1947,1956 (Box-folder 55:13)
    - Chapter Records Reports 1929,1930 (Box-folder 55:14)
    - Chapter Records Sectional Conference 1930-1931 (Box-folder 55:15)
    - Chapter Records Questionnaire 1933 (Box-folder 55:16)
    - National Chapter Records 1926 (Box-folder 55:17)
    - National Chapter Records 1927 (Box-folder 55:18)
    - National Chapter Records 1929 (Box-folder 55:19)
    - National Chapter Records 1950 (Box-folder 55:20)
    - National Chapter Records 1952-1953 (Box-folder 55:21)
    - National Chapter Records 1955 (Box-folder 55:22)
    - National Chapter Records 1955 (Box-folder 55:23)
    - National Chapter Records 1956 (Box-folder 55:24)
    - National Chapter Records 1957 (Box-folder 55:25)
    - National Chapter Records 1957 (Box-folder 55:26)
    - National Chapter Records 1967 (Box-folder 55:27)
    - National Chapter Records (Box-folder 55:28)
    - National Chapter Records-Printed 1926-1949 (Box-folder 55:29)
    - National Chapter Records-Printed 1962-1967 (Box-folder 55:30)
    - National Chapter Records-Printed (Box-folder 55:31)
    - National Chapter Records-Printed (Box-folder 55:32)
    - National Chapter Records-Bulletin 1937 (Box-folder 55:33)
    - National Chapter Records 1946-1947 (Box-folder 55:34)
    - National Chapter Records 1954,1959,1961 (Box-folder 55:35)
      - Journals April 1924 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1925 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1926 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1927 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1928 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1929 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1930-1931 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1932-1933 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1947 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1948 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1951 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1952 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1971 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1925 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1927 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1928 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1930 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1932 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1933 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1946 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1947 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1951 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1952 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1953 (Page 56)
      - Journals April 1954 (Page 56)
      - Southeastern Sectional Conference 1957 (Page 56)
      - Va State Branch-Founders Day Tea 1951 (Page 56)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority